- [Narrator] It's like you're screaming
and no one can hear.
(somber music)
You almost feel ashamed
that someone could be that important,
that without them you feel like nothing.
No one will ever understand
how much it hurts.
You feel hopeless
like nothing can save you.
And when it's over and it's
gone, you almost wished
that you could have
all that bad stuff back
so that you could have the good.
(thunder roaring)
(upbeat electro music)
♪ Yellow diamonds in the light ♪
♪ Now we're standing side by side ♪
♪ As your shadow crosses mine ♪
♪ What it takes to come alive ♪
♪ It's the way I'm feeling
I just can't deny ♪
♪ But I've gotta let it go ♪
♪ We found love in a hopeless place ♪
(upbeat electro music)
♪ Shine a light through an open door ♪
♪ Love and life I will divide ♪
♪ Turn away 'cause I need you more ♪
♪ Feel the heartbeat in my mind ♪
♪ It's the way I'm feeling
I just can't deny ♪
♪ But I've gotta let it go ♪
♪ We found love in a hopeless place ♪
(upbeat electro music)
♪ Yellow diamonds in the light ♪
♪ Now we're standing side by side ♪
♪ As your shadow crosses mine ♪
♪ Mine, mine, mine ♪
♪ We found love in a hopeless place ♪
(upbeat electro music)